Mistress, spank my bottom. Spank it really hard!
女主人  打我屁股  用力打
Please, spank my bottom!
请打我屁股
- That is unpleasant. -Spank it really hard.
-真恶心  -用力打
Lick my nipples.
舔我乳头
No, thank you, pregnant lady.
不了  谢谢  胖女人
Strip, soldier!
脱衣 士兵们
You're gonna find out why they call me the drill sergeant.
你们就会知道为什么他们叫我操练军官
That's... that's nice, baby.
真爽  宝贝
No, Frizzy! no!
不要  卷毛  不要
No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
不要  不要 不要 卷毛  不要弄
Frizzy.
卷毛
No, no, no, wait! Cody! No.
不要 不要 等等 科迪 不要
No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
不要  不要  不要  卷毛  不要
Don't worry about it, man. Everyone's got a sex tape.
别担心  伙计  谁都有性爱录像
Please.
算了吧
Yeah, except they're having sex with people.
是阿  只是他们是跟人在做爱
-Frizzy. - Right.
-卷毛  -对
It's not technically incest
如果你的家庭是特殊物种的话
If your family member's a different species.
理论上不算是乱伦
So, are you getting close with Dana yet?
所以  你跟达娜有什么进展吗
The rumours are true. She's taken the pledge.
谣言是真的  她发誓禁欲
No sex? She was your sure thing.
禁欲  你对她可是很有把握的啊
-Faith-camp propaganda, man. She's waiting until marriage.
-信念夏令营的宣传  伙计  她等结婚后再做爱
I thought she had sex with six guys.
我以为她和六个男生做过爱
What?
怎么了
Get to class.
进教室去
No cell phones in the hall, Alyson.
走廊上不准用手机  艾莉森
You can pick this up from my office today after school.
放学之后去我办公室拿
No, no, no,Frizzy! No! Frizzy!
不要  不要 不要  卷毛  不要 卷毛
Well, I've seen worse.
我还看过更糟糕的
No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
不要  不要  不要  卷毛  不要
Miss Johnson. Lunch today?
约翰逊小姐 一起吃午饭吗
I'll have to check my calendar, perv...Pete.
我得先看看日程表  变态...皮特
No, no, no, Frizzy! No! Frizzy!
不要  不要  不要  卷毛  不要  卷毛
Look. Look. Look at that.
看  看  看这个
- Hey, just ignore them. -Oh, god. You saw it, too?
-嘿  别管他们  -噢  天啊 你也看到了
Just so you know, it's not at all...
你知道 那不是
Hey, don't worry about it.
不要紧
Frizzy's a good-looking dog.
卷毛是只很好看的狗
So, do you wanna do it? Are we on?
所以  你想做吗  我们上吗
Rob? Rob? Are we on for seventh period?
罗伯  罗伯  我们上不上第七节课吗
Yeah. l...i'll...
好  我
- I'll meet you over there. -Okay.
- 我等会去找你  -好
- Doggy style! - Hey, stifler.
-狗交狂  -嘿  斯戴福尔
Is that your girlfriend?
那是你女朋友吗
No, we're just...we're just...we're friends.
不是  我们  我们只是  我们只是朋友
Just friends? How sweet.
只是朋友  真好
Well, she seems awful ripe.
她看上去真成熟
If you don't pick the fruit, I will.
如果你不偷禁果  那我就偷了
Hey, beautiful.
嘿  美女
Good morning, east great falls blazers.
早上好  东大瀑布高中的开拓者
Don't forget about the big game against central this week
别忘了本周对抗中央高中的比赛
And the aloha dance this friday from 7:00 to midnight.
欢迎舞会从晚上七点举办到午夜
Hawaiian shirts and leis are recommended for entrance.
建议入场的时候穿戴夏威夷衫和花环
- Charles, knock that off. -Sorry.
-查尔斯  关掉那个  -不好意思
Let's focus on the quiz, please.
请专心考试
Douche bag.
混蛋
I'm serious about this pledge, you know.
你知道  我是认真发誓的
I know.
我知道
- So just dancing tonight. - Yeah. Just dancing.
-所以今晚我只跳舞  -行  只跳舞
The horizontal hula.
横向呼啦舞
Nathan.
内森
Poor Nathan.
可怜的内森
His willy must be hard enough to cut glass by now.
他的小弟弟肯定硬得能够割草了
Nathan loves me, and nathan respects me.
内森爱我  也很尊重我
Okay. A, a guy never respects a girl enough to give up sex.
一  男人永远不会尊重一个不要性爱的女人
And, B, well, what about you?
二  那你呢
You must be feeling pretty randy by now, Dana.
你现在肯定觉得性欲特强吧 达娜
Okay, well, yeah, maybe, like, the tiniest bit,
好吧  可能有那么一点点吧
But I really feel like I'm connecting with the higher power here.
但我真觉得自己有极强的控制力
Yes, I know, and that is totally fab,
是  我知道  这非常好啊
But I know I couldn't do it. I'm way too into giving blow jobs.
我就不行了  我太热衷于口交了
Ask Richard.
问问理查德就知道了
Hey, don't listen to Lmogen, okay?
别听伊莫金的好吗
Sex is a really big deal, and if you feel like you're not ready,
性爱还是很重要的  如果你觉得还没准备好
Then I think you should wait.
那我认为你应该再等等
But...
但是
No offence,Heidi, but you have no idea what you're talking about.
无意冒犯  海蒂  你根本不知道自己在说什么
Text me later.
等下给我发短信
-Hey, Rob. -Yeah?
-嘿  罗伯  -怎么了
-Can I ask you something? - Sure. What's up?
-我可以问你一些事吗  -当然  什么事
Well, it's kind of personal.
个人的一些事情
Okay.
没问题
I've been thinking. You know I'm a virgin, right?
我一直在想  你知道我还是处女吧
It's just...I don't know.
只是  我不知道
Everyone's already done it like a million times already,
好像别人已经做过一百万次爱了
And I know I don't have a boyfriend or whatever, but...
我知道我还没有男朋友  但是
But sometimes I feel like I should just get it over with.
有时候我感觉我应该去试试
You know? I mean, just get past this whole thing, this virgin.
你知道吗   我是说我想破处
What does that even mean, anyway?
那到底是什么意思呢
So I've never had a penis in my vagina, but so what?
还没有小弟弟插进过我阴道  但是那又怎样
Why do I have to label everything? like, "She's too innocent."
为什么我要记得这些事  比如  她太单纯了
She can't handle it.
肯定不能做爱
I'm not that innocent.
我一点都不单纯
I've seen Showgirls and Blue Lagoon.
我看过《脱衣舞娘》和《蓝色珊瑚》
Anyways, I think I've decided to just do it. But what do you think?
总之  我决定去试试  你觉得怎么样
Yeah. I think you should definitely go ahead and get it over with.
是啊  我觉得你应该把这事给做圆满了
Thanks.
谢了
Let's get back to work.
回到学习上去吧
Stifler  coming at you live from the aloha dance
斯戴福尔正在欢迎舞会上为你做现场直播
Here at the east great falls...
这里是东大瀑布
This chick just grabbed my ass.
这个妞刚刚抓了我屁股
She wants to play the stifmeister's flute skin.
她想玩玩斯戴福尔的小弟弟
Let go find some of that sweet-looking pinoche, Gibbsy.
一起去找找那些长相甜美的美女吧  吉普西
Hey, check it out. There's Heidi.
看那边  海蒂在那里
All right, all right. She looks highly doable.
不错  不错  她看上去容易得手
All right, so what's the game plan here?
所以游戏计划是什么
I don't know. Ask her to dance, I guess.
我不知道  我想应该请她跳舞
You need a plan, all right?
你得有个计划  知道吗
It's all about establishing your intentions.
这样你才能建立目标
See, right now, she thinks of you as just a friend.
看  现在  她只觉得你是个朋友
You need to break that paradigm.
你需要打破这个形象
Remember, friends don't let friends just be friends.
记住  朋友不会让朋友只是朋友
-Right. - I'm serious. you cannot puss out here.
-没错  -我说真的  你别搞黄了
All right, take it easy. I'm gonna go talk to her.
知道了 别紧张   我会去跟她说的
Wait. Aren't you forgetting something?
等等  难道你没忘记什么吗
Here, don't forget these.
这里  可别忘了这个
You only need those when you're alone.
这是你孤单的时候需要的东西
Right. Right. Okay.
对  对  好吧
-Okay! -What? What's wrong?
-好了  -什么  怎么了
I can't.
我不能
-But it's only second base. -I know. But if we go there,
-才到二垒  -我知道  但是如果我们进行到那里
Then we're gonna wanna go further.
我们会更深入进去的
But Adam and Eve did it.
可亚当和夏娃都做爱了
I'm sorry. Hey, hey.
对不起  嘿
I love you. Do you know that?
我爱你  你知道吗
Come here.
来吧
Is god okay with a blow job?
那上帝接受口交吗
I thought you understood how I felt about this.
我以为你知道我有多在乎这件事
I told you, it's important for me
我告诉你  结婚前
To save myself until marriage.
保持贞操对我来说很重要
You've had sex with seven guys.
你都跟七个男生做过了
And it was six, not seven!
是六个  不是七个
Well, one was a black guy, so he counts as two.
其中一人是黑人  他一人顶两人
Dana.
达娜
-Dana, come on. -Fuck off.
-达娜  别生气  -滚开
Dana. Come on, Dana. Dana!
达娜  过来吧  达娜  达娜
Hey, girls. This is gonna be for sit-on-my-face-book.
嘿  小妞们  这个会放到我的脸书网上面
I need you to kiss one time, okay?
你们亲一下好吗
I don't know.
我不知道
Come on. It's gonna be seen by millions of people.
来吧  数百万人会点击看的
Okay.
好吧
Okay, we're gonna go again,
好了 我们再来一次
But this time, sneak in some tongue for daddy.
但是这一次   给爸爸伸出舌头
Okay.
好吧
That's what I'm talking about, baby!
我说的就是这样  宝贝
Stifmeister strikes again!
斯戴福尔再次袭来
Dude.
伙计
You're gonna love this. Check this out.
你肯定会喜欢这个  看看吧
Yeah. So?
是啊  所以呢
Watch and learn.
看着跟我学学
"You're hot."
你真性感
"Give me your number "
给我你的电话号码
"And let's get together"
一起出去玩吧
I throw this at a hot girl,
我把这个丢给一位辣妹
And she's so impressed that
然后她很有兴趣
I'm literally throwing around a benjamin
我的阴谋就得逞了
That she wants to hook up with me.
接着她会想认识认识我
Yeah. Good luck with that.
好吧  祝你好运
-I'm gonna go find dana. -All right, man.
-我要去找达娜  -好吧
Oh, no.
糟了
Oh, god.
天啊
Excuse me, excuse me, Watch out. Coming through.
借过  借过  小心  有人要过去
So, I was thinking about what
我在想之前说的那些话
We were talking about, you know, before.
你知道之前那些
-Yeah. Yeah, I remember. -Right. So I was thinking, why wait?
-是的  是的  我记得  -好  所以我想还等什么呢
Right? I mean, you might as well, you know, get it over with.
对吗   我是说你也想了却这么一桩事
What? Like, here? At the dance?
什么  在这里  舞会上吗
Well, there's always the library.
通常都是在图书馆
-Yeah, the library. - I'm kidding.
-对  图书馆     -我开玩笑的
-Yeah. I know. -But seriously, after the dance,
-我知道  -但是说真的  舞会完了之后
I don't know if you...
我不知道是否你
-What are you doing? -Looking for my money.
-你在干什么  -找我的钱
-C-note thing? -Yeah.
-那一百块吗  -是的
-Lose your money? -Shut up.
-钱没了吗  -闭嘴
And we're back. What's up, dude? Where's Heidi?
回神啦  怎么了  伙计  海蒂在哪
I don't know.
我不知道
She was here a second ago. Maybe she went to the bathroom.
她几秒前还在这  可能上厕所去了
-Yeah, maybe. -Dana's pissed at me.
-是啊  可能     -达娜现在很生我气
Dude, you gotta play along with this whole pledge thing.
伙计   你得陪着她守住誓言
Well, that's easy for you to say.
对你来说是简单
You haven't exactly broken the seal yet, either.
你也没有真正搞到她啊
Dude, I've been getting to third base on a regular basis.
伙计  我平时都能打到三垒
I can't go back to jacking off now.
而且我现在都不打飞机了
Dude, just use your left hand. It feels completely different.
伙计  你用左手打飞机会有很不一样的感觉
-I'm gonna go find Heidi. -I'm gonna go find Dana.
-我要去找海蒂   -我也去找达娜
No! dude, you're gonna make me hurl.
小子 你差点把我推倒
Heidi?
海蒂
No, no, no, no!
不要  不要  不要
Wait.
等等
Dude, yo.
兄弟  嘿
What are you doing?
你在干什么
Rob? you said...
罗伯  你说
Rob!
罗伯
Dude, nice cock block.
兄弟  来的真是时候
I'm on fire.
我着火了
- I'm on fire. -Oh, my god.
-我着火了  -天啊
There's a fire. there's a fire, and it's on me.
着火了  着火了  我身上着火了
Oh, my god.
我的天啊
Rob! Rob! put it out. Take off your pants!
罗伯  罗伯  把它扑灭  把你裤子脱了
Take off...Take your pants off!
快脱了  把你裤子脱了
Oh, god!
天啊
Come on!
快点
Oh, my god. Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
我的天啊  我的天啊  我的天啊
Hurry, Rob, Come on.
快点  罗伯  快
Get it out! Get it out!
把火熄灭   把火熄灭
Oh, god.
天啊
What the hell is going on in here?
该死的  发生什么事了
Two months seems like an awfully
为期两个月的每周六
Long time for saturday detention.
留堂也太长了吧
We're supposed to clean up the library.
我们应该是去打扫图书馆
Do you guys know where the vacuum is?
你们知道吸尘器在哪吗
Nope.
不知道
What were you doing in the library anyway?
你当时到底在图书馆做什么
I wasn't doing anything. Heidi was already in there.
什么都没做  当时海蒂已经在那了
-I was just looking for her. -I heard she was blowing some dude.
-我只是去找她  -我听说她在帮某男口交
Cody! well, I don't know how you're
科迪  如果你被留堂的话
Gonna go on the school ski trip
我不知道
If you're still on detention.
你还怎么参加学校的滑雪旅行
Mom, I don't see what that has to do with it. I didn't do anything.
妈  我不懂两者有什么关系  我什么都没做
I heard you were the fluffer.
我听说你就是那个男的
-Cody. -Look. Lis lips are chapped.
-科迪  -看  他的嘴唇都裂开了
Well, we'll see.
再看吧
All right. I have to go get ready.
好了  我要去准备一下了
Maybe it's in the garage.
可能吸尘器在仓库
Rob? I wanna have a little chat with you.
罗伯  我想跟你谈谈
Do we have to?
我们有什么好谈的吗
Honey, I know that you're growing older,
亲爱的  我知道你长大了
And I don't know what your father has told you about things,
我不知道你爸爸跟你说过什么
But I think it's important to discuss everything, you know?
但是我觉得什么事都应该讨论讨论
Like about sex.
比如说性
-Are you having sex? -Mom, I don't wanna talk about this.
-你做过爱了吗  -妈  我不想讨论这个事
No, well, it's just that I found this sock in the laundry, and, well...
不是  我只是在洗衣的时候找到条袜子  而且
Oh, god, mom. Put that away.
天啊  妈  把它扔了
And, also, somebody sent me a link to this video.
还有  有人给我发了个视频的链接
No, no, no, Frizzy! No.
不要  不要  不要  卷毛  不要
-Mom, just turn it off! -I don't know how!
-妈  把那东西关了  -我不知道怎么关
Your brother made it my start-up screen.
你弟弟帮我打开的
-Okay, I can...I can fix that. You can? Great.
-好了  我能  我能弄好  -你能  太好了
-Yeah. -Thanks.
-好  -谢谢
-No, no, no, Frizzy! no! -Thank you for that.
-不要  不要  卷毛  不要  -谢谢你了
-Okay. -And we're done. right? Yeah.
-好吧  -所以我们讨论完了  对吗
Well, honey, please. There's no reason to be ashamed.
亲爱的  这没什么好羞愧的
Masturbation is perfectly natural.
手淫是很正常的事
I mean, boys your age are maybe into experimentation
你这个年纪的男孩都会想试验一下
And trying new things with animals.
跟动物尝试些新东西
I mean, Frizzy, she's been in our family for...
卷毛  我是说她还是小狗的时候
Since she was a puppy...
就来我们家了
Hey, I'm late.
我要迟到了
-You're tardy. -Sorry.
-你来迟了  -不好意思
You can start by cleaning off all the damaged books
你先从清理那些烧过的书开始
And separating the ruined ones. I'll be checking on you.
然后把坏的分类出来  我会随时检查
Heidi. Look, about last night...
Heidi 听着 关于昨天晚上
I don't wanna talk about it.
我不想谈那个
-Well, I just wanted to tell you... - Rob.
-我只是想告诉你  -罗伯
I'm gonna go empty this bucket.
我去倒脏水
Do you have any idea what I found here?
看我找到了什么
This is the Bible.
这可是《索爱天书》
I thought that was an urban legend.
我以为这只是个都市传说
No. This is real. This goes back decades.
不  这是真的  这可以追溯到几十年前
Okay. So what?
那又怎样
This is exactly what we need to finally get laid.
这书可以帮我们把到妹
How is this thing gonna help us get laid? It's ruined.
这东西怎么帮我们呢  它全毁了
You can't even read most of it.
大部分都看不了
This book has helped one lucky guy
这书每年都帮了
Each year at Great Falls.
学校里的一位幸运儿
And this year, that lucky guy is us.
今年我们就是幸运儿了
Even with the damage,
虽然这书残缺不全
It still has a ton of useful stuff.
可还是有很多有用的内容
Check this out.
看这儿
"February 1st, 1977. The G-spot:"
"1977年2月1日  G点"
- I can dig it. - What else you got?
-这个我也懂  -还有什么
"1991. How to shave your pubes
"1991年  如何刮阴毛
to make your dick look bigger"
使小弟弟看起来更大"
Dad showed me that one.
我爸指导过我这个
"2003. I just had the most amazing sexual experience"
"2003年  我经历了最棒的性体验"
Something I can't read. "She used a breath mint"
一些看不清了  "她用了薄荷糖"
A breath mint? For what?
薄荷糖  干嘛的
You moron. You stick it up your tailpipe and
你傻啊 在勃起以后
The minty-ness makes your asshole twitch.
薄荷糖能让你的菊花更紧
Everyone knows that.
大家都知道啊
Dude, I don't know. This sounds pretty weak.
我可不知道  听起来不怎么样
Plus, I mean,
话说  我觉得
We can find most of this stuff on the internet anyway.
这些大部分都能在网上找到
No, this is different. This has personal experiences.
可不一样  这些都是个人经验之谈
Plus, it's custom-tailored to Great Falls girls.
而且  这是为大瀑布高中女孩而写的
Since when does Punani have a zip code?
什么时候普纳尼镇有邮编了啊
What have we got to lose?
我们有啥损失呢
Nathan, you've been working on Dana for, what?
内森  你和达娜在一起多久了
Like six months?
六个月了吗
Only to find out that she loves the lord more than sex?
才发现她喜欢上帝比喜欢性更多吗
And, lube, how have all your schemes
卢贝  你这学期计划中的
To get laid been working out so far?
把妹进展如何了
Minus $100.
损失了100美元
Exactly, and me, well,
没错  还有我
I've been wasting all my time
我一直都在
On some fantasy that someday
浪费时间幻想
Heidi's gonna fall madly in love with me.
哪天海蒂会爱得我不能自拔
Face it, guys, we need help.
醒醒吧  兄弟们  我们需要帮助
And this is it, staring us right in the face.
而机会就摆在我们的面前
- I'm in. - All right.
-我加入  -很好
I'm in.
我也加入
- Yeah. - Yes.
-耶  -太好了
- Yeah! - Yeah!
-耶  -耶
Hey, easy. Guys, it's old.
别激动  兄弟们  这书很旧了
"May 1st, 1990.
"1990年5月1日
"The simplest way into a girl's pants is still basic flattery"
"把到妹最简单的方法就是讨好她"
That's it? Just flatter her?
就这样吗  讨好她吗
How many times do you actually do it?
你真这么做过几次了
Walk up to a girl and say, "Wow, you have beautiful eyes"
走到一个女生面前  然后说  "你眼睛真好看"
Like, never.
好像从来没有
It's telling us the only proven way
这告诉我们把妹最有效的方法
To get women is to be an asshole,
就是要猥琐
'Cause the guys that actually
因为只有那样的男生
Spew that kind of crap get laid.
才能把到妹
Check it out. Twelve o'clock.
快看  12点方向
- All right. Let's put this bible to a test. - Yes.
-好吧  让我们试验下这本书  -好
- You go talk to her. - I'm not trying it out on Ashley.
-你去和她说  -我才不要找艾什莉试
Why don't you go talk to her,
为什么你不去
'cause you're the one who likes her?
你不是喜欢她吗
- I'm eating. - Okay. I'll do it.
-我还在吃呢  -好吧  我去
Hey, Ashley.
嗨  艾什莉
Hey, Rob. Shopping for your girlfriend?
嗨  罗伯  给你女友买东西呢
No...This is...It's for my mom.
不  这个  是给我妈的
She's dating again.
她又开始约会了
Well, you know, I... Actually, I wanted to say,
呃  其实  我想说
You know, you have the most gorgeous teeth.
那个  你牙齿长得很美
Hey. Come with me.
跟我来
Jealous? He's making a move on your lady friend.
嫉妒了吧  他跟你的梦中情人走了
Unlike you, I don't mind sharing my women.
才不像你  我不介意分享我的女人
And what are you wankers up to today?
猥琐男  你们今天要干嘛呢
- Cheerio. - Hello, love.
-你好啊  -嗨  亲爱的
Word to your mumsie.
代我向你妈问好
Just waiting for some ladies to join us, in fact.
事实上  我们在等某些女士加入呢
You nancy boys couldn't get laid
你们这些娘娘腔
At a Jonas brothers concert
别想凭着后台通行证
With a fistful of backstage passes.
就在乔纳森兄弟的音乐会上搞到女人
Cheerio.
拜拜了
Was that a slam?
她在鄙视我们吗
You bet your bollocks.
别自己损自己了
- Hold this. - Yeah.
-拿着  -哦
How does this look?
这个怎么样
Stand up.
站起来
Wait, what...what's...Wait, hold...hold on.
等等  什么...  那个...  别别
Should I call you?
我是要打电话给你吗
Just walk out of the store and meet me at the food court.
走出商店然后去美食区找我就好
Act natural.
自然点
Can I help you?
需要什么帮助吗?
Okay, then.
好吧
- Have a nice day. - You, too.
-祝您愉快  -你也是
I'm sorry! I wasn't stealing. It was a...it was a prank.
抱歉  我什么都没偷  这只是个恶作剧
I am so sorry. I think we left the tags on your garments.
抱歉  我想我们忘了给你的商品消磁了
Please come back to the register. We'll figure this out.
麻烦到收银台来  我们会帮您解决的
I'm so embarrassed.
实在抱歉
Oh, my god.
我的天哪
Sorry, l...i got excited.
对不起...  我有点兴奋了
That'll be 149.90.
149.90美元
- How much? - 149.90.
-多少  -149.9美元
But they're so small.
就这么小的东西
- Thank you. - Have a nice day.
-谢谢  -祝您愉快
Come again.
欢迎下次再来
What took you so long? Did you get it?
怎么这么久  搞定了吗
Sure did. I even stole you a bag
当然 我还帮你偷了个袋子
So you don't have to touch it till you get home.
你回家之前都不用碰到它
Great. Thanks.
很好  谢了
Hey. What's up, Ashley?
嘿  你好啊  艾什莉
What are you pillow biters doing here?
你们几个同性恋在这个干嘛
Stifler.
斯蒂夫勒
Don't eat that. You're gonna get fat.
别吃那个  会增肥的
I'm super horny. Wanna suck me off in the Sharper Image?
我超级饥渴  想去夏普专卖店搞我吗
Okay.
好啊
Dana. Excuse me. I'm so sorry.
达娜  打扰了  真抱歉
Didn't mean to disrupt the... This morning's mass.
我不是故意要扰乱...  晨间弥撒的
What are you doing here?
你来做什么
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
我是来道歉的
Did you really think
你觉得现在适合
That this is the best time to discuss this?
说这个吗
Well, you weren't answering any of my texts.
可是你都不回我短信
What is faith?
什么是信念
When you flip the light switch in your kitchen,
当你按下厨房灯的开关
You know that the light will turn on.
你知道灯会亮
Some might call that faith,
有人说这就是信念
but I tell you, that is not the real faith.
但我说  这不是真正的信念
Okay, so what is so important
好吧 什么事这么重要
That you needed to come and interrupt church?
非得你打断弥撒
I don't really get why you're so mad at me right now.
真不明白你现在干嘛这么生我的气
Because you don't respect me.
因为你不尊重我
This is all just a big joke to you.
对你来说只是个大笑话
You know what? You're right,
知道吗  你说得没错
Because this is just another face for you.
这就是你的另一面
Just like your little stint on yearbook.
就像你在做年鉴的时候一样
You stuck with that for, what,
一开始坚持  然后呢
Two weeks before you got bored with it?
两周以后就厌倦了
Why is it so hard for you to believe that I wanna
为什么让你相信我希望等到结婚后
Wait until marriage?
再做这件事这么难
Because you slept with Doug Wheeler.
因为你一个晚上同时和道格・威尔勒
And Scott Thompson on the same night.
还有斯科特・汤普逊睡过
That doesn't count: I was drunk.
那不算  我喝醉了
Is that Dana?
是达娜在说话吗
As soon as you get bored with this whole pledge thing,
一旦你厌倦这个誓言之后
You're just gonna jump right back in the saddle again.
你就会回到之前的状况了
And when you get to college, don't even tell me
等你到了大学  别告诉我说
That you won't be experimenting
你没和女同性恋
with the standard lesbian hookups,
尝试过交往
Having three-ways, trying anal.
3P  还有肛交
- Yeah. - Yeah.
-耶  -耶
That's what I'm talking...
我就说嘛
Just relax.
放松
- Do something! - Faith is...
-别愣着啊  -信念是...
Faith is the rock-solid...
信念坚如磐石...
You don't think I'm committed to this?
你不相信我是认真的吗
My parents waited until marriage.
我父母就等到结婚后才做
My dad went to high school with your mom.
我爸和你妈一起上的高中
He said she blew the whole football team
他说她上过整个橄榄球队
And had to have her stomach pumped.
搞得不得不去洗胃
Don't be gross, okay?
别这么恶心行不
Plus, your dad was a beta.
另外  你爸只是替补
Those guys are notorious poon slayers.
那些家伙可是性交好手
Fuck it! This is bullshit!
他妈的  全是胡扯
You know you want this.
你知道你想这么做
Did we miss communion?
我们错过圣餐了吗
Go for the East Great Falls Blazers
东大瀑布高中的开拓者加油
Go, Blazers!
加油  开拓者
Which is surprising,
令人惊讶的是
since this is the last home game of the season.
鉴于这是本季最后一场主场比赛
You'd think they'd really pump up the power there.
他们使出了全部的力气
Look at him! Watch that guy! Watch that guy!
小心  盯住他  盯住他
Even though it's close to a tie,
尽管现在比分接近平局
Oh, my gosh, wait. So, what did your dad say?
哦  天哪  对了  你爸刚才说什么
He said if he ever sees Nathan within 100 feet of me,
他说如果再看到内森在我100英尺内出现
He's gonna castrate him with a rusty garden weasel.
他会用生锈的园艺工具把他阉了
Oh, no. So what? Is it over between you guys or what?
不是吧  那你们结束了还是怎样
I don't know.
不知道
Well, if you ever want to try a mage,
如果你想整他的话
You're welcome to join Richard and me.
欢迎加入我和理查德
- No. - No.
-别  -不用了
Please don't say "young boy" around Coach Daly.
别在戴利教练面前说"年轻男孩"
Yeah, out here he's...
没错  他是...
- What about you, missy? - What?
-那你呢  美女  -什么
How's your sex life?
你的性生活啊
You guys, I'm gonna go through with it. I am. I am.
拜托  我打算开始性生活  是的  没错
You're so boring.
真无聊
I would've thought you'd be fielding offers
我以为你在图书馆脱衣服后
After your striptease in the library.
早就已经都搞定了
Blue and white, let's go, fight, win.
蓝白军  先前冲  加油  必胜
Let's go, fight, win.
向前冲  加油  必胜
Blue and white, let's go, fight, win. Blazers!
蓝白军  向前冲  加油  必胜  开拓者
Fight, win. Blue and white, let's go, fight, win.
加油  必胜  蓝白军  向前冲  加油  必胜
I think that is quite enough pictures of the cheerleaders.
我想你拍啦啦队拍得够多了吧
How about we get some of the game?
应该多拍点比赛吧
As you were.
继续
Douche bag.
蠢货
Blue and white...
蓝白军
Shearson's bringing the ball up court.
希尔森把球带到了前场
He passes it off to Scott Stifler.
把球传给了斯科特・斯戴福尔
Central takes a charge from Shearson.
中心高中队拦下了希尔森的球
Time out, Blazers. What are we gonna do now, bill?
时间到  开拓者  现在该怎么做呢  比尔
Ten seconds in the game.
离比赛结束还有10秒
I think these guys really need to get their act
我想他们该好好努力打下去
Get your head in the game, doggy style.
用心比赛  傻子
You can finish your wet dream later.
你可以比赛完了再做你的春梦
- I'm sorry. - This is it for this game.
-对不起  -比赛情况就是这样
Hey, Scott? Can I talk to you for a sec?
嗨  斯科特  我能和你说两句吗
Are you nuts? I'm in the middle of a game.
你疯了吗  我还在比赛
Last home game of the season.
本赛季的最后一场主场比赛
Really gotta get their act together.
真的让他们好好行动起来
Tie game, 89 all, 3:9 seconds left.
89平  还剩3.9秒
Let's see what's gonna happen here.
看看会发生什么
They have the advantage.
他们现在占优势
Looks like... Double screen!
看起来...  双掩护
Shearson gets the ball. It's good! It's in!
希尔森得球了  太好了  进了
The game's over. 91-89 for East Great Falls Blazers.
比赛结束  91比89  东大瀑布的开拓者获胜
This is incredible, folks!
不可思议  朋友们
This means we're going on to the playoffs!
这意味着我们打入季后赛了
Unbelievable! It's exciting.
不可思议  太激动了
What a chain of events that has occurred here today!
今天发生的这些太美妙了
Honey, I need to talk to you.
亲爱的  我们得谈谈
Yeah, sure.
哦  好的
Is...is that a bible?
那个...是圣经吗
What? No. No, it's...
什么  不是  这是...
Well, honey, it's okay to read the bible.
亲爱的  读圣经没什么不好啊
I mean, gosh, you act like
我的意思是  你表现得
I caught you reading pornography.
像我抓到你读色情书
What did you wanna talk about?
你刚要说什么来着
Well, I just got my credit card statement and...
我刚收到我的信用卡账单
And here on your card
你的刷卡记录里
There's a charge here for a lingerie store.
有项来自内衣店
Is there a girl you're seeing?
你谈恋爱了吗
No. Mom, it's complicated.
不是  老妈  这很复杂
- did you buy something for yourself? - no!
-你是买给自己的吗  -不是
Because it's a very normal area of exploration.
你对这方面好奇很正常
My book says that
书上说
Most fetishes are not homosexual in nature,
某些恋物癖不代表就是同性恋
And, well, you know, boys, they tend to...
而且  你知道的  男孩子么...
Yes, mom, that's it. You figured it out.
好了老妈  没错  你说的对
I love wearing women's underwear.
我就是喜欢穿女性的内衣
Thongs, g-strings, a little teddy now and then.
小内裤  丁字裤  还有连衫衬裤
It's so soft and silky smooth. The frillier the better.
穿起来又软又滑  有花边的更好
Sexy.
淫荡啊
Oh, god! Come on.
天哪  拜托
Gotcha.
搞定
So it was for a girl.
所以是给女生的咯
Yeah, mom.
是的  老妈
Great.
很好
So, you know that thing you told me before the dance?
你还记得在舞会前你和我说的话吗
Yeah.
记得
Right, well, I was thinking about that conversation.
好吧  我在想你说的那些话
So, what about it?
怎么了
I was just thinking, you know, maybe you should wait.
我在想  我觉得  你或许该等等
But I still feel like I'm making this whole thing
但我一直觉得这整件事
Into, like, this huge deal.
好像  变成了一个大问题
I mean, it's consuming my every thought.
我的意思是  它一直困扰着我
I don't know, Rob.
我不知道该怎么做  罗伯
I still feel like it's best if I just get it over with.
我总觉得搞定这件事是最好的
Yeah. I can see that.
没错  我懂
You figured it out. I love wearing women's underwear.
你说的对  我就是喜欢穿女性的内衣
Thongs, g-strings, a little teddy now and then.
小内裤  丁字裤  还有连衫衬裤
It's so soft and silky smooth. The frillier the better.
穿起来又软又滑  有花边的更好
What is up with this crap, butt nugget?
这是什么东西  蠢货
That was taken completely out of context.
这完全是断章取义
All right? I was being facetious.
我当时说的是玩笑话
That means he wasn't being serious.
他的意思是他不是当真的
I know what facetious means, dick face.
我知道玩笑是什么意思  蠢货
Are you trying to repel all the pussy in school?
你是想全校的女生都讨厌你吗
- No... - Tick tock, doggy boy.
-不是  -滴答滴答  和狗搞的人
You cock is on the clock.
性福时间到
Excuse me. Take notes.
让一下  记得做好笔记
- Hey, Imogen. - Stifler.
-嗨  伊莫金  -斯戴福尔
The word for the day is legs
今天的关键词是腿
So?
所以呢
So, why don't we go back to my place
为何不去我那
And spread the word?
探讨一下这个词
Well, how about you save your breath?
为什么你不省口气
You're gonna need it to inflate your date later.
还是留着对你的马子说吧
Gentlemen, it is time we got laid.
绅士们  是找个妞上床的时候了
Really? And what is it we've been trying to do all this time?
是吗   我们不是一直想这么做吗
No, no. We need to get laid.
不不  我们得做爱
Right here. September 9th, 1995.
这写着  1995年9月9号
Can you give us the executive summary?
你能不能说个简洁扼要的纲领
No, not that. This.
不  不是那个  看这
We are going on a road trip.
我们得来次公路旅行
How long do you intend on staying in Canada?
你们打算在加拿大呆多长时间
Just a couple of hours.
就几个小时
What's the nature of your visit?
你们来这干什么
We've driven many miles in search of vertical smiles.
我们驱车好几百英里来这找辣妹
We use kilometres here.
这用的是公里
Then we've driven many clicks to wet our dicks?
那我们驱车几百公里来这润滑一下老二
Yes! Yeah!
是这样
- That works, right? - Bye bye.
-这行得通吧  对吧  -拜拜
Fucking Americans.
操你们美国佬
You know, the exchange rate
加拿大的外汇率
On the dollar is really gonna help us out.
真的能帮我们解决不少问题
Yeah.
是的
Okay, up ahead, turn right.
好的  前面路口右拐
- You sure? - Yes. Turn right.
-你确定吗  -是的  右拐
Okay, boys. Let's do this.
好的  伙计们  我们开始吧
Are you sure this is a good idea?
你确定这是个好主意
Come on, you pussy. Let's get laid.
快点  孬种  我们去找点乐子
The bible says to ask for Monique.
性经上说我们得找莫妮克
Hi. Are you Monique?
嗨  你是莫妮克吗
No, moi, no, no, no. mais,
不不不不...
Monique, she is inside.
莫妮克  她在里面
Come. Come, boys.
进来  进来  小伙子
Boys, entrez chez nous.
小伙子们  这是我们的房子（法语）
C'est magnifique, no?
很漂亮  不是吗
I will get Monique.
我这就去叫莫妮克
She will be so happy to see you.
见到你  她肯定会很高兴
In the meantime, make yourselves at home.
在此期间  请自便
Jesus, tits.
天啊  真是波涛汹涌
We came to the right place.
看来我们是来对地方了
Is that a moose?
那是头麋鹿吗
Condom?
要套套吗
Why, thank you.
为什么  谢谢
Gentlemen.
先生们
Thank you.
谢谢
Very much.
很感谢
Can't wait to see Monique.
真想快点见到莫妮克
We're here to see Monique.
我们是来找莫妮克的
I am Monique.
我就是莫妮克
Well, that's...that's okay.
那...挺好的
Come, come. I make you a nice drink.
过来  过来  让我给你们倒杯美酒
Could you just give us just one minute?
你能给我们一分钟时间吗
This could be very educational for all of us.
也许能够让我们学到不少知识
Really?
是吗
He's up.
他准备好了
No, no. Why am I first?
不不  为什么我第一个
It was your idea.
这是你的主意
Don't...don't insult Monique.
不要...欺负莫妮克
She has an entire chapter in the bible.
她可在书里占了整整一章
Come on, you're going to have a nice time.
快点  你会很享受的
You two crazy kids have fun.
你们两个疯子玩得开心
And welcome.
热烈欢迎
So...so, how does this work?
那...应该怎么做
Am I supposed to pay you?
我该付你钱吗
No, no, no. Not yet.
不不不  现在不需要
I see.
我明白了
You've got one active imagination, boy.
你是在做白日梦呢  年轻人
How long was I out?
我出神多长时间了
Only about eight seconds that time.
这次只有八秒钟
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. no. no. no, no, no.
不  不  不  不  不...
Yes. yes.
对  对
Monique! That's really nice.
莫妮克  做得太赞了
That's it.
就是这样
I'm so sorry. I usually last a lot longer.
很抱歉  我一般会挺很久
Hey.
嘿
Hey, was I supposed to tap you on the shoulder or something?
嘿  我该拍一下你的肩或是什么吗
Oh, no. No.
哦  不要啊
Help! help! help, help, help!
救命  救命  救命  救命
Go, go, go! go! I'm coming!
快  快  我来了
- Jesus. Dude. - Oh, god!
-我的天  伙计  -上帝啊
What, do you need an audience?
怎么了  你难道还想要个观众吗
No, no. Wait, guys.
不  不  等等  伙计
I think she's dead!
我猜她是死了
Excuse me?
你说什么
Oh, my god. This is not good.
天啊  这可不妙
I can't get her off.
我甩不开她
I think she had a heart attack.
我估计她是突发心脏病了
Help!
快来帮忙
she's got lockjaw.
我猜她是得了牙关紧闭症
Get her off of me!
快帮我把她弄开
oh, my god. oh, my god.
哦 我的天啊
It's lockjaw.
是牙关紧闭证
Lockjaw! Lockjaw, lockjaw, lockjaw, lockjaw, lockjaw!
夹住了  夹住了  夹住了  夹住了
- Okay. - Get her off!
-好吧  -快帮我弄开
I'm sorry!
抱歉
Phone. Phone. Wait. Clear!
电话  电话  稍等  让开
Shit. What am I doing?
该死的  我在干什么
Clear, clear!
让开  再来一次
Okay. Come down here.
好的  从下面入手
Grab her legs. One, two, three.
抓住她的腿  一二三
Forget it. It's totally screwed up.Oh, god.
算了吧  完全被卡住了  上帝啊
What you do to maman?
你们对妈妈干了什么
Maman! You killed maman!
妈妈  你们杀了妈妈
You killed maman!
你们杀了妈妈
Fucking Americans! Come back here.
操你们美国佬  快给我滚回来
I'll kill you! I'll kill you, you cowards!
我要剁了你们  我要剁了你们这群懦夫
I killed her.
我杀了她
I killed her with my sperm!
我的精液把她害死了
Hey, man
伙计
When it's your time to go, it's your time to go.
阎王要你二更死  不会留你到五更
She led a full life.
她人生已经很完整了
How do you know that?
你怎么知道
Man, what do you want me to say?
伙计  你想要我说什么
You're the one that murdered her!
说你杀了她吗
I can't believe that was the woman
真不敢相信
The bible said we should have sex with.
她就是性经上说的做爱对象
Right here,"September 9th, 1995:"
这儿  1995年9月9号
Let me see that.
我来看看
No. no, that's a seven!
不  不  那是7!
That's 1975. It's from the '70s.
是1975  是70年代
- I thought it was a nine. - Shut up! Shut up!
-我以为是九  -闭嘴  闭嘴
I didn't do anything!
我什么也没做
Shut up! Just shut up! I wanna go home.
闭嘴  闭嘴  我想回家
I don't wanna be here.
我不想来这
Oh, my god! I just hit a squirrel.
上帝啊  我刚刚碾了只松鼠
Well, that went well.
投得不错
Guys, I think it's time we try my interpretation.
伙计们  现在得按照我说的做
Look, Nathan
听着  内森
You've been trying to convince Dana to sleep with you
你想说服达娜和你上床
Instead of just listening to her. Right, you know?
而不是对她言听计从是吧
Trying to see things from her point of view?
为何不从她的角度考虑一下
Showing just...
给她...
Just a little respect.
...一点点的尊重
And you, you're still
还有你
Trying to trick women into sleeping with you
你还在引诱女孩子和你上床
Instead of just being honest.
而不是坦诚相待
And you're still too much of a pussy
你还不是个不敢告诉
To tell Heidi you're into her.
海蒂自己喜欢她的孬种
You going to Stifler's house tonight?
你今晚会去斯戴福尔那吗
Yeah. I'll probably go with Dana.
是的  我有可能和达娜一块
So any luck losing that thing you were trying to get rid of?
那个你想赶快解决的事有什么进展吗
- Rob. - I'm just asking.
-罗伯  -我只是随便问问
Maybe you should mind your own business.
也许你该少管闲事
What's with you today?
你今天怎么了
I wanna tell you something that
我想跟你说件
I've been wanting to say for a long time.
很早之前就想告诉你的事
Okay.
好的
I really like you.
我很喜欢你
I really like you, too.
我也很喜欢你
No, not like that. I really like you.
不  不是那样的  我是真的很喜欢你
- Rob... - I think you're great.
-罗伯  -我觉得你很棒
You have a great personality. I laugh at all your jokes.
你性格好  很会说笑话
You're pretty.
还有你很漂亮
Oh, god, you're pretty. You even smell great.
天啊  你很漂亮  闻起来都这么香
I don't know. I'm just...
我不知道  只是...
I'm happy when I'm around you.
和你在一起很快乐
Now, I don't know if you feel the same way
我不知道你是否有这样的感觉
but if you do...
如果有的话...
Let's not waste any more time.
那我们就不要再浪费时间了
Right? let's just
好吗  我们...
See where our feelings take us.
试着跟着感觉走
I feel the same way.
我也有同样的感觉
- You do? - Yes.
-真的吗  -是的
This is great. Why didn't you say something?
这太棒了  你为什么不说呢
Why didn't you?
你为什么不说
It's about that time, so I gotta go. but I'll see you tonight?
时间到了  我得走了  晚上见
Yes.
好的
Dad?
爸爸
There she is.
她过来了
They saw me! Get down! Get down!
他们看到我了  快蹲下  蹲下
Oh, my god. Oh, my gosh.
哦  上帝啊  上帝啊
Drive. drive.
快开车
It's cool. It's cool.
没什么  没什么
Nathan, look, I've been thinking.
内森  听着  我在想
Maybe I've been too hard on you.
或许我对你太苛刻了
You have?
有吗
You obviously love my daughter,
看得出你喜欢我女儿
And you two should be together.
你们应该在一起
- We should? - Absolutely.
-我们应该吗  -当然
Honey, it is not right to give a man blue balls.
亲爱的  这样招待人家可不对
If you want boys to like you
如果你想男孩子喜欢自己
you gotta put out.
就得秀出来
Here, start with nathan's friend.
先从内森的朋友入手
This is so not cool.
这真是逊毙了
I mean, fantasising about your best friend's girlfriend?
意淫你死党的女朋友吗
Oh, my god!
哦  上帝啊
- Dad! Stop! Stop. - Fucknut!
-爸爸  不要  -操你他妈的混蛋
All right, girls.
好的  女孩们
- Party looks good. - Yeah.
-派对看起来不错  -是的
All right, listen to me. Stay focused.
听我说  集中精神
Be honest, show respect
坦白点  尊重对方
And just say whatever's on your mind.
说出自己心声
Stop, jerk.
闭嘴  混球
I can't even get near Dana.
甚至都不能接近达娜
She'll be here. She's coming with Heidi.
她很快就到  和海蒂一起
Just try and think of things from her point of view.
尽量设身处地为她着想
Yeah, and I might as well just crack the da vinci code
这点如果我在行的话
While I'm at it.
达芬奇密码早被我解出来了
Just get her some frankincense and myrrh.
给她送点乳香精油和没药
That's a great idea.
好主意
I'll just pick up some roofies for you while I'm out.
如果不奏效的话我会给你好果子吃
You need a prescription for that, from what I hear.
据我所知  那得有配方才行
Lube, pay attention. This applies to you, too.
卢贝  听仔细  这对你也有用
All right. Let's try to go in there and just be real.
我们进去后  尽量保持自我
All right, Oprah.
好的  奥普拉
Hey. Isn't that that chick from Central?
嘿  那不是从中心高中来的妞吗
Yeah.
没错
Hey, Stifler.
嘿  斯戴福尔
Oh, hey, there...
嘿  你叫
Katie.
是凯蒂
Katie, right. I knew that.
对  是凯蒂  我当然知道
Just having some fun with you.
只是和你开个玩笑
Can I talk to you for a second, like, in private?
我能和你谈谈吗  就我俩的谈话
Yeah, sure, you know what?
可以  你知道吗
Let me just grab another beer and I'll be right back with you.
我再去拿杯酒  随后就来找你
Don't you flake on me.
不要放我鸽子
- Dude, you been working out? - Didn't think so.
-伙计看来收获不错  -我不这么认为
- You two, stay amazing. - My god.
-你们两个真能扛  -上帝
Hey, what's up, beautiful?
嘿  怎么样  美人儿
You know, I got so drunk last weekend
我上周末烂醉如泥
That I nailed my cock to a table
结果把自己的小弟弟钉在桌上
then set it on fire.
放在火上烤
Wanna check it out?
想检查一下吗
The table or your cock?
检查桌子还是你的老二
God, I love that accent.
天啊  我爱死那个腔调了
Could you do me a favour and just say,
你能够帮我个忙  说一下...
"spank me, Stifler. "
"打我的屁股  斯戴福尔"
"Spank me wee little bum."
"打我的小屁股"
How did you know I like to be spanked?
你怎么知道我喜欢被人打屁股
Awesome!
太棒了
So where's this boyfriend Richard you
那个你一直叨叨念念的
Keep talking about non-stop all the time?
男友理查德哪去了
He doesn't attend high-school parties.
他不参加高中派对
Sounds like you might be
听起来你是想要些
In the market for some home-grown American beef.
国产的美国牛肉啊
Sorry, I'm vegan.
对不起  我是素食主义者
Cheers.
干杯
What if I use a cucumber?
那用黄瓜行吗
All right, boys. Tonight's the night.
伙计们  就在今晚
Wish me luck.
快祝我好运
Good luck, buddy.
祝你好运  伙计
Tonight, you become a man.
今晚  你将成为真正的男人
That's it. Tonight, I'm getting laid!
说得对  今晚  我要做爱
- Yeah, buddy! Yes! - Yeah, buddy.
-是的  伙计  -是的  伙计
- Yes! - Right here.
-是的  -就在这
Just give it to her nice and slow at first.
开始的时候慢点温柔点
Then speed her up.
然后加快节奏
Dana!
达娜
I can't find Heidi anywhere.
我找遍了  没见到海蒂
Maybe she didn't come.
或许她根本就没来
No, no. Her car is outside.
不  不 她的车就停在外面
How you making out?
你认为是怎么回事
Check it out.
看那边
Don't you think maybe
你难道不觉得或许
Ashley's just a little bit out of your league?
艾什莉对你来说太有难度吗
I don't know. I'm just saying, you know
我不知道  我只是想说
You've been at it for years.
你已经盯上她好几年了
Maybe it's just not in the cards for you.
或许你和她之间没有可能
I'm a man of refinement.
我是个有修养的人
Why settle for a six when you can get a perfect 10?
能得十分为什么要去得六分呢
Okay, whatever you say, man. Good luck.
好吧  随便你怎么说  祝你好运了
Right. I'm gonna do it.
我要行动了
Hey, what's up, ashley?
嘿  你怎样  艾什莉
Hey, Lube.
嘿  卢贝
You want a beer?
要啤酒吗
Got a beer.
有了
Right.
对
So...
那么
You obviously know that I'm, like, totally into you. Right?
你肯定知道我非常喜欢你  对吧
Yeah. I've seen the Shrine.
是啊  我去求过签的
All right.
好的
Okay, so I'm just gonna be honest with you.
那我就跟你坦诚布公
I'm just gonna lay it out on the line.
实话实说
No tricks, no hidden agenda at all.
并且毫无保留的
I happen to be a sensitive and expert lover.
我碰巧是个敏感专业的情人
I can guarantee that I will satisfy you in every way possible,
我保证让你爽到极限
And I shall not stop until I'm certain
在你飘飘欲仙之前
That you are completely happy with my endeavours.
我绝不会停止
Okay.
好的
Look, that was a really interesting speech,
听着  说得真吸引人啊
And I don't really wanna embarrass you in front of
我也不想在
everyone, but...
众人面前让你出丑
But it's not gonna happen.
但我们之间是不可能的
I mean, I think that you're, like, really super cool,
我是说  我知道你超酷
And you're really funny in class and everything,
班里班外看起来也都很可爱
But I don't wanna have sex with you.
但我不想跟你做爱
Okay?
明白吗
Yeah, yeah. Sure. Okay.
当然  当然  好的
- So are we cool? - Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
-没事吧  -当然  当然
All right.
好的
Well, I'm gonna go get another beer. Do you want one?
我要再去拿杯啤酒  你还要吗
No, no. I'm...I'm good. I'm good.
不  不  不用了  谢谢
What you said just now?
你刚才说什么
Yeah?
怎么了
Was that true?
是真的吗
Guaranteed satisfaction and you won't
保证满意而且绝不
Stop until a girl is completely satisfied?
停止除非女生爽歪之后
Yeah.
当然
All right. Well, what the hell.
那好吧  管它呢
Meet me upstairs in the first bedroom to the left.
到楼上左边第一间卧室找我
The truth is, yes, I was trying to pressure you,
事实上  我一直都对你施压
Because I really, really wanna have sex.
因为我太想  太想做爱了
But I really wanna have sex with you.
但我只想跟你做爱
And, also, I mean, with us,
而且一直以来
hooking up has always been about me.
约会也总以我为中心
I wanna forget myself for once
我想改变一下
And try to make you feel good for a change.
来好好满足一下你
Like, maybe try and make you feel the way that
就像  让你满足我那样
You make me feel.
满足你
You shouldn't...You shouldn't... It's my phone.
别看  别看  那是我的手机
Don't read my phone.
别看我的手机
What's this supposed to mean? "Give her a dose of manthrax"?
这是什么意思  "给她一剂炭疽病毒"
Well, I don't...what does that...
我不知道  我也不知道什么意思
I don't know what that... Do you know what that means?
我也不知道  你知道吗
"I'm getting laid"?
"我要上床了"
You're advertising this before it even happens?
还没发生你就到处宣扬
- No. - Wow.
-不  -哇
You must be some special kind of asshole.
你还真是个怪异的变态
No. no, no, no! no. I didn't...It was...
不  不  不  不  我没有  那是
Later, loser.
等着吧  你个败寇
Faster. Okay. Now, slower. Yes, Yes.
再快点  好的  现在  慢点 就这样
Slower. Tickle the bunny. Yes, Yes.
再慢点  舔外阴  对  就这样
Oh, God, the man in the boat is out.
天呢  开始高潮了
Paddle, paddle, do the Alphabet. Swirl.
继续  继续  口交舌功  打卷
Back to the bunny. That's it. Okay. Now, more to the left.
回到外阴那  太爽了  往左边移
More to the left!
再往左点
- My left or your left? - My left, my left, my left!
-我左边还是你左边  -我左边
All right.
好的
Hey, have you seen Heidi?
嗨  看见海蒂了吗
Thanks.
谢谢
Hey, Rob.
嗨  罗伯
Heidi?
海蒂
Hey, doggy style. I told you, you snooze, you lose.
狗仔  告诉过你  打个盹你就输了
So unless you want mop-up duty, close the door, pervert.
若不想看我们做爱  就走人  变态
Hey, where are you going?
你去哪
This was a horrible idea.
这个主意太差劲了
Rob? Excuse me.
罗伯  借过一下
Excuse me. Rob. Rob.
借过一下  罗伯  罗伯
- Go away. - I didn't. I...
-走开  -我不想
I don't wanna see your face right now.
我现在不想看见你
Rob.
罗伯
What are you doing?
你在干什么
What happened to forgetting about yourself
你不是说不管自己
And making me feel good?
就让我爽吗
But I thought I just...
但是我想
What? You thought that what, Nathan?
什么  你想什么  内森
That you could just pretend that you cared about
你就假装关心我的想法
My feelings and my pledge
在意我的誓言
And then just go and try again when my guard was down?
然后再趁机占我便宜吗
No. You don't get it. I...
不  你没明白  我
No. no, you're the one that's not gonna get it.
不  不  是你没搞明白
Dude, you need to slow down.
兄弟  你要悠着点
Yeah, seriously. Let's just go home.
是啊  真的  我们还是回去吧
You, Sir... you, Sir, were right about the Bible.
对  对  关于《索爱天书》  你说的对
Because assholes get laid!
因为贱人喜欢做爱
Yes.
对
No. no, no, dude. You were right.
不  不  不  兄弟  你才是对的
- There's something to it. - What are you talking about?
-里面蕴意深刻  -你在说什么
We tried the nice guy thing
我们试着做好男
and I believe we're all still virgins.
还保留着处男身
Well, the nice guy vibe got me past the bouncer, man.
而这种好男情怀让我越界了
Well, gentlemen, you failed,
绅士们  你们都输了
And the proof, as they say, is in the jell-o.
因为你们都嫉妒
So I will see you later, nice guys.
兄弟们  一会见
I know you want me.
我知道你对我感兴趣
I'm gonna let you take me upstairs and do me right now.
我跟你上楼  让你爽死
- Really? - Yeah.
-真的  -当然
Kiss me.
吻我
Hey, ladies.
嗨  女士们
Oh, my god.
哦  天啊
Look at those taters!
瞧瞧这帮骚女
Do me from behind.
从后面干我
What?
什么
I thought you liked it doggy style.
我以为你喜欢后进式
What are you doing back there? let's go.
你在那干什么呢  进来啊
You're not putting your dick in that, are you?
你不会把你的弟弟插进去是吧
Are you kidding me? Gross.
你搞啥  太恶心了
Here. This'll help.
给你  喝点这个有好处
Thanks.
谢谢
Honey, I know that
亲爱的  我知道
I can't stop you from doing certain things,
我不能阻止你做某些事
But I can insist that you are safe.
但你一定要注意安全
Did you drink and drive?
你有没有酒后驾车
No. John Costello drove me home.
没有  约翰・卡斯特罗开车送我回来的
I want you to know that
我只是想告诉你
if you find yourself in any carnal situation,
即便欲火焚身
That you...You will use protection.
也要注意安全措施
What do you mean by carnal?
你说欲火指什么啊
This.
这个
Are you kidding me? gross.
你搞啥  太恶心了
Is there no such thing as privacy any more?
现在还有隐私没有
I will tell your father that
我会告诉你父亲
You're just not up to seeing him today.
说你今天不能见他
You're not feeling well.
你不太舒服
Thanks.
谢谢
How was she?
她怎么样
- How was who? - Vomit girl.
-谁  -你吐的那个女孩
How do you know about that?
你怎么知道
Who do you think is forwarding all those videos to mom?
那你认为是谁把这些视频给妈妈看
I'm ready to give up.
我要放弃了
I thought I had the answers.
我认为我知道问题答案了
It's too bad that 99% of the Bible's completely unreadable.
《索爱天书》99%都不能读
That's it.
这样好了
We need to reconstruct the Bible.
我们来重编《索爱天书》
Why?
为什么
The secrets are in there.
因为秘密都在这
I mean, there's no one single answer to getting laid.
想要上床不是一下两下能搞定的
Right? We need the whole book to understand.
对吧  我们需要通读才行
Probably has a lot of crap in there that we need to know, too,
说不定还有好多我们需要知道的呢
Like positions, techniques, angle of insertion.
比如位置  技巧  插入角度
Exactly. That's what the Bible was created for,
没错  《索爱天书》就是
To help guys like us.
给我们这种人看的
And we owe it to the others. I ruined the bible.
我们亏欠别人  是我毁了这本书
I owe it to future generations to restore its wisdom.
为了未来的人  我也要恢复这本书的精华
Dude, I'm all for it, but how?
哥们  我也想这么做  但怎么做
Where do we start?
从谁开始
From the beginning.
从最早开始
This must be the guy who created the Bible.
肯定是这个人创了《索爱天书》
Hello?
哪位
Hi, may I speak to Noah Levenstein, please?
您好  请问诺亚・莱文斯坦在吗
Speaking.
请讲
Are you the one who created the Bible?
是你创了《圣经》吗
No, that would be God.
不  应该是上帝
Hold on.
等等
I'm referring to the Bible.
我指的是《索爱天书》
I'm calling from east great falls high school.
我是从东大瀑布高中打来的
It was the summer of my junior year, 1969,
那是1969年高三夏天
And my buddies and I, we take this trip to Amsterdam,
我跟朋友一块去阿姆斯特丹玩
Where we run into a group of semi-attractive Dutch nymphos
碰上一群还不错的荷兰淫女
Who were willing to trade their bodies for
愿意卖身换一把
a handful of Jimi Hendrix LPS.
吉米・亨德里克斯LPS系列电吉他
Well, needless to say,
毋庸置疑
we had ourselves one super weekend with those gals,
那个周末我们和那群小妞玩的超爽
Sexually speaking, if you get my drift.
我指性趣上  如果你理解我说的
But the sad news was, we had no idea what we were doing.
但不幸的是  我们都懵懂无知
We had no technique.
什么技巧也不会
And then one day, we were out sight-seeing,
但有一天  我们外出观光时
And we run into this dutch hooker in the red-light district,
我们在红灯区碰上一个荷兰妓女
And she tells us about this book.
她跟我们提起有这么一本书
It was a sex manual,
一本性爱指南
evidently written in the 19th century by some priest.
是由19世纪某个牧师写的
Well, we read that thing cover to cover,
我们详读了一遍又一遍
And then when we got back to east great falls,
然后回到东大瀑布高中
I had the bright idea to write my own book
我有了写一本自己的书的想法
And add my own observations and experiences and advice
写上自己的观察  经验和建议
And leave it in the library for some
然后把它留在图书馆
Other hapless virgin in the class below us.
给那些不幸处男后辈们
But I had no idea it had been passed down for 40 years.
但我没想到居然流传了40年
Your book is a legend, Mr. Levenstein.
您的书简直是个传奇  莱文斯坦先生
Do you have it here?
你们带了吗
Yeah.
带了
May I see it?
我能看一下吗
Oh, my.
哦  天啊
Boys.
孩子们
This is a real piece of history here.
这可真有点历史了
What happened to it?
它怎么了
Well, that's why we're here.
这就是我们来的原因了
The Bible kinda got ruined,
《索爱天书》有点被毁了
So we wanna call everyone on the list and try to reconstruct it.
所以我们想咨询相关作者来进行重编
Well, I think you boys might need some help.
那看来你们是需要帮助了
Well, girls have the advantage,
女孩们通常有优势
because girls talk to each other,
因为她们会彼此聊天
And don't kid yourself, they talk about the penis.
不是跟你们开玩笑  她们连阴茎都聊
Penis size, penis shape, the angle of the bend.
阴茎大小  形状  弯曲角度
Whether it winks at you. they talk.
不管你注意没注意的  她们都聊
Now, to really make love to a woman,
真要想跟女人做爱
You gotta really care about her.
首先要真正关心她
But...hey, sex is great,
做爱很爽
But sex with someone you love? That's awesome.
但跟你爱的人做爱才最爽
Dude, that is so profound.
哥们  这太有意义了
Telling you.
我说嘛
Yeah, definitely gets lonely on the road.
是啊  在路上难免会感觉孤单
Sure, I made love to all kinds of different food groups.
当然  我用个各种食物自慰
Did you ever try making love to a peanut-butter sandwich?
你试过用花生酱三明治做爱吗
Nothing comes close.
超爽
What?
什么
Well, maybe a deboned ham hock,
也可用去骨蹄膀
But that takes a whole lot of prep.
不过准备起来太麻烦
Bend your knees.
屈膝
Next time you spank it, sit Indian-Style.
下次做时  试试印度式
You won't come, not in a million years.
即使是一百万年都不会泄
Our sex organs are like musical instruments.
我们的性器官就像音乐器材
Sure, you can have any technician blow on your horn,
你可以请任何技术员来帮你吹喇叭
But to place your instrument into the hands of a true expert?
但把乐器放入一位真正的专家手中呢
That, my young friend, is true harmony.
年轻的朋友们  那才是真正的和声
Guys don't talk to each other
男孩们从不交流这方面的事情
Because they view each other as competitors,
因为他们视彼此如对手
Which I think is crazy. You know?
尽管我觉的这很荒谬
Because men need to help each other and work together
男人们也需要同心协力
To get laid.
如果想把到妹
Noah Levenstein, class of '70.
诺亚・莱文斯坦  70级
- Pete Sambrelli? - That's right, the Noah Levenstein.
- 皮特・萨姆布雷利  -没错  诺亚・莱文斯坦
Do you have a number for him?
你有他的电话吗
This is regarding his advice on the lubricants.
这是一些关于他对润滑剂的使用建议
We found the tongue tornado in Regina.
我们在女王篇发现了舌转风暴功
You said bros befo' hos.
还说为朋友两肋插刀
Isn't that what you said? bros befo' hos.
是不是你说的  为朋友两肋插刀
And then you screwed my girlfriend.
那你还上了我女朋友
Well, so did the entire glee club, Carlito.
卡里托  合唱团的人都是这样啊
What's your point?
你什么意思
It's all about chemistry, and confidence is the key.
都是生理需求  但信心是关键
R-e-s-p-e-c-t, you've heard that song, right?
相敬如宾  你听过那歌  对不对
Boys, we got another confirmation.
孩子们  我们又确认一个
You gotta treat your lady right.
你要正确的对待你的小姐客户
You've got to be gentle, kind
你需要温柔和蔼
And respectful to the one you love.
并且尊重你爱的那个人
- Who are you talking to? - Shut the fuck up.
-你在跟谁打电话  -闭嘴
This is how you get her really excited.
这样你才能让她芳心欲动
Stick your finger in her ass. Trust me.
把你的手指插入她的屁眼  相信我
Was that two fingers or one?
用两根还是一根手指
I'm sorry. Confidential matter.
对不起  那是机密
Phone, phone. Okay.
电话  电话  好的
Then what happened?
然后呢
Hello. Yeah. Class of '77.
你好  对  77级的
Yeah, hold on. Let me get a pen.
等一下  我找只笔记下
Pete O'donnell, please.
请皮特・奥唐奈听电话
Who is this?
你是谁
Mr O'donnell, this is Marshall Lubetski.
奥唐奈先生  我是马歇尔・卢布斯基
I just wanted to talk to you about what you wrote in the Bible.
我想和你交流一下《索爱天书》的内容
You know, about having anal sex with Miss Johnson.
你知道的  是关于你和约翰逊女士的肛交
Thank you very much! Mark S.!
非常感谢  划掉马克 S.
This is not a sex manual.
这不是一本关于性的手册
It is a life manual.
这是人生手册
Now, I've been married for 35 years
我结婚已经35年了
And not just because I'm this handsome dude
没有离婚不仅是因为我帅
Who knows how to satisfy a woman.
知道怎样满足女人
I've been married 35 years because I love my wife
35年不离不弃是因为我爱我的妻子
And I respect my wife.
我尊重她
And whether it's Amsterdam or East Great Falls
无论是在阿姆斯特丹还是东大瀑布高中
It all comes down to this.
都因为我爱着她
If you're honest and treat a girl with respect,
如果你真诚并尊重女孩
Then whatever happens is meant to happen,
该发生的就会发生
Because it's all perfectly natural.
因为这一切都是自然而然的
Boys, I've prepared you for this quest.
孩子们  兵马未动粮草先行
And before you lies the biggest test of your lives.
在你面前的是人生最大的考验
This book is a powerful weapon,
这本书是强大的杀手锏
So use it for good
好好地利用它吧
Not evil.
别适得其反
Yes.
太好了
You still looking for the vacuum?
你还在找吸尘器吗
No. I found it in Cody's room. So strange.
没  很奇怪它在科迪的房间里
I mean, I just don't remember leaving it there.
我是说我都忘了放在那里了
Losing my mind, clearly.
显然我糊涂了
Hey, mom, can I go on the ski trip?
妈妈  我可以参加滑雪旅行吗
Yes.
好
But no drinking, and if you do drink, no driving.
但是别喝酒  如果喝了别开车
Don't worry. If I do anything wrong
别担心 如果我做糗事
I'm sure it'll end up on youtube, so.
Youtube上肯定马上就有了
Call you when I get there.
到了给你打电话
Drinking round!
喝酒的环节到了
- Deal me in. - What are you doing here?
-我也要参加  -你在这里干嘛啊
Katie.
我叫凯蒂
I know. But what are you doing here?
我知道  但你在这里做什么呢
- I wanna play. - Right.
-我也想参加  -好
Just deal her in, Stifler.
斯戴福尔  让她参加吧
What's the big deal?
有什么关系呢
Yeah, deal her in.
让她参加吧
Hi, Nathan.
内森
Thanks for the flowers.
谢谢你的花
I'm sorry about being a jerk.
我为我以前的行为道歉
And, for the record, I've learned my lesson.
而且我已经自尝苦果
I'm ready to respect you and support you on your pledge.
我会尊敬你并支持你的的誓言
Really? But why?
真的吗  为什么呢
I'm in this for you. I'm not in it just to have sex.
我是因为你  而不是性这么做的
Well, I realised that I'm in this for you
我意识到我是因为你才这么做
And if the pledge gets in the way of that
如果誓言祈祷了某种作用
then how good can it really be?
那这个作用会有多好的效果呢
Sounds like a good basis for the two
我们两个好像结成了统一战线
Of us to just relax and see what happens.
我们好好玩静观其变
Look. I bought a book.
看我带来一本书
I was thinking that we could
我正想我们两个
Start on page one and then
可以从第一页开始然后
see how far we get this weekend.
看周末我们能读到哪里
The first three chapters are foreplay.
前三章是前奏
You know, I've actually been reading a book, as well.
你知道吗  我也正在看一本书
Have you ever heard of the Tongue Tornado?
你听过舌转风暴吗
Okay, let's go.
我们走
This is supposed to be fun.
这肯定很好玩
This isn't fun.
一点都不好玩
Just you wait. You possess wisdom now.
等一下  你现在智力无边
Trust in the book.
相信这本书吧
I mean, what does that mean, anyway?
我想问那到底什么意思呢
Do you think I'm too clingy?
你觉得我会不会太粘人了
No. no, of course not.
当然不是
Do you even know how to play poker?
你知道怎么打扑克吗
I know the game.
我知道这个游戏
And I tell you what, if I lose, I'll take off all my clothes.
如果我输了  我就脱光衣服
Snap. Nice.
哟  棒极了
And if I lose?
那我输了呢
You apologise to me.
向我道歉
- For what? Blowing you off?  - Yes.
-为什么呢  甩了你  -对
If it's not enough, it was my first time.
道歉还不够  那是我的第一次
I deserve better.
你应该给我更多
But if I win, not only do you apologise to me
如果我赢了  你不仅要道歉
You gotta run through the snow naked.
你得全裸在雪地里跑
- Yeah. - It's a deal.
-太棒了  -一言为定
Start stripping, sweetheart.
亲爱的  开始脱衣服吧
It's not over yet.
还没有结束呢
Feeling lucky?
运气好吗
You better hope for a five on the river, baby.
你最好期待会有一个5
She got the five! Unbelievable.
她真拿到了5  太不可思议了
Oh, my god.
天啊
- Strip. - Hold on a second.
-脱掉  -等一下
- Strip. - Strip.
-脱掉  -脱掉
strip! strip! strip! strip!
脱掉  脱掉  脱掉  脱掉
You want me to strip? You want some of this?
你们想让我全裸  你们想看吧
It's time to get it going, baby!
宝贝们  我真脱了
All right, let's go! here we go, baby.
好啊  我们走
Wait, let's talk this over.
等一下  我们再谈谈吧
Shit. it's freezing out here.
该死的  外面冷死了
Now apologise.
现在道歉
- I'm sorry. - For what?
-对不起  -为什么呢
I'm sorry for not calling you afterwards.
因为之后我没有给你打电话
And what else?
还有呢
I'm sorry for being a dick, okay?
我猪狗不如  好了吧
Now, open the stinking door.
现在  打开这该死的门
Open the door!
开门
Now, tell everyone how you cry like a little girl after you come.
告诉所有人你进来后会如何哭
I cry like a girl after I come, okay?
像娘们儿一样哭好吧
It's a very intense experience for me.
那可是我的极限了
Call 911 .
报警
Hey, I'll meet you at the lodge later.
待会去屋里找你
Yeah, yeah, sure. go.
好啊
Heidi. Wait up.
海蒂  等一下
Do you mind if I ride up with you?
你介意我和你一起坐吗
Okay.
不介意
Hey. What's up?
还好吗
We...we're in the same gondola.
我们一起坐缆车
Yeah, look at that.
对啊
Oh, god.
天啊
I didn't sleep with Stifler.
我并没有和斯戴福尔上床
Yeah. I heard.
嗯  我听说
- But you still hate me? - No.
-你还在讨厌我吗  -没有啊
No. Why would you say that?
你为什么这样说呢
You haven't said a word to me since that night.
那晚后你都没和我讲过一句话
I know. I'm sorry.
我知道  对不起
I guess I just... I needed time to work through my feelings.
我觉得我需要时间整理一下思绪
And? What did you decide?
然后呢  决定什么了吗
Gibbs says that Stifler has to sit
吉布斯说斯戴福尔不得不
On a foam rubber doughnut for six weeks.
在泡沫橡胶甜甜圈垫子上坐六周
And he says they're talking about
他说斯戴福尔
Amputating his feet from frostbite.
因为冻伤要截肢
Gibbs is a liar. Stifler doesn't need amputation.
吉布斯是骗子  斯戴福尔不用截肢的
That's too bad. I got an A in shop.
那可太坏了  我在商店里做爱都得过A
Oh, my. Was that a snort?
天啊  那是喷鼻声吗
Come to gloat?
心满意足了吧
No. Just looking for a fag.
只是在找同性恋罢了
Just 'cause I took a moose pickle up my ass doesn't mean I'm gay.
我和一只麋鹿做了并不代表我是同性恋
Very funny. How's your bum?
很搞笑  屁股怎么样了
Feels like I gave birth to a mayonnaise jar, but thanks for asking.
好像生了一堆蛋黄酱  不过谢谢关心
Hey, I heard about your boyfriend. that really sucks.
我听说了你的男朋友  真要命
Yeah. I thought only high school boys were jerks.
我还以为只有高中男生是混蛋呢
It turns out they never outgrow it.
事实并非如此
Lmogen, no offence, and
伊莫金 希望你不介意
you're the most mature girl I know,
你是我见过最成熟的女孩
But a 24-year-old dude isn't gonna take a high-school girl seriously.
但是24岁的男人不适合你
I suppose not.
我想不是吧
You wanna sit down?
要坐下吗
What for?
为什么
I just thought we could both use a friend right now.
我认为我们可以共同用一个朋友
Stifler.
斯戴福尔
My bad. reflex.
我错了  本能反应
I'm sorry.
对不起
You have to make your own decisions.
你得自己做决定
You know, I just... I thought we had something.
我还以为我们关系非同寻常
We did.
我们以前是啊
We do.
现在也是
I was scared.
我很害怕
Of what?
为什么呢
I really like you.
我真的喜欢你
And I want it to be special.
我只是想初夜非同一般
I guess I just wanted to be ready.
我只想做做准备工作
So you almost had sex with stifler so you'd be ready for me.
你和斯戴福尔上床只是为我做准备工作
Yeah.
对
That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
这是我听过最蠢的话
Well, I heard you got some practise.
我听说你有过些经验
You know, the truth is, is nothing happened.
其实事实上是什么也没有
I didn't want it to be random like that.
我不想那么随意
And...
而且
I couldn't picture my first time being with anybody else but you.
我不想我的第一次给除了你之外的人
What was that?
怎么了
I don't know.
不知道
- Looks like we're stuck. - Yeah.
-好像我们被困住了  -对
You know, we could be up here for a while.
我们可能会在这里待上一段时间
Yeah.
对
Hey, can I ask you a question?
我能问你一些问题吗
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
对  随意问
Why do you hook up with assholes like scott stifler anyway?
你为什么和像斯戴福尔那样的人渣搞在一起
Excuse me, but you don't know me.
你说什么啊  你都不了解我
You know, you're just the same as all the rest.
你和其它人都是一样的
I'm just some sort of trophy to you.
我只是一种战利品
You don't care about me. You just wanna sleep with me,
你并不关心我  只关心和我睡觉的事
Because you think it's some sort of status symbol.
你认为这是值得炫耀的事
Sorry.
不好意思
God.
天啊
How long are we gonna be up here?
我们会在这里待多久呢
I'll get help.
我来求助
What are you doing?
你要干嘛
It's not that far down, and there's, like, 20 feet of snow.
这儿并不高  而且有20英尺左右的雪
What, is this supposed to impress me?
这是你想在我面前表现的吗
The thought had crossed my mind.
曾经想过
Absolutely not. first of all, it's just wrong.
别这样做  第一  这是错误的
Second of all, you're not even supposed to touch the door.
第二  你都不能碰到那扇门
And third, it's just really dangerous, okay?
第三  这十分危险
So just get away from there.
别这样  过来
Right. What was I thinking?
对啊  我在想什么呢
Are you okay?
你没事吧
I think I hurt my leg.
我的腿好像受伤了
Idiot.
笨蛋
Are you okay?
你没事吧
Are you crazy?
你疯了吗
Yeah, I'm fine. no, I'm fine. I'm fine.
没事  没事
About what you said about how I don't care about you
你刚刚说我不关心你
And you're just a trophy, that's actually not true.
你只是一个战利品  那都不是真的
I really like you. We went to elementary school together.
我真的喜欢你  我们一起上的小学
I remember when you sang Hey Ya! in the sixth-grade talent show.
我还记得你在六年级表演唱的《嘿  你好》
I remember when you fell off the pyramid at the homecoming game
我还记得你在回家游戏中从金字塔上摔下
Freshman year.
大一的时候
You were so embarrassed, but I didn't care.
你当时很  不过我不介意
I just liked how you played it off like it was all part of the routine.
摔下就好像是你表演的一部分
I mean, yeah, sure, you're a super-hot babe,
是啊  你是学校的风云人物
But I actually like you for you.
我只是喜欢你这个人
Look, this may be a shock to you,
可能你会觉得很突兀
But I have no idea what I'm doing with girls.
但我不知道怎么和女孩交流
But I really wanna learn.
我真的想好好学学
You just give me a chance.
你给了我机会
That's all I'm asking.
这是我所有的愿望
And I guarantee that I will make it my life's mission
我保证我会为你的幸福
To satisfy you in every way possible.
奋斗终生
- Let's go back to the... - to the cabin.
-走  我们回去  -回到缆车上
Dude. You forgot to sign it.
伙计  你忘了签字了
You sure we can't just keep it for one more year?
你确定我们不能再留它一年吗
No, guys, it's someone else's turn.
不能  轮到其他人了
Rob on computer. This is my little brother, Cody,
这是我的弟弟科迪
And this is what he does with the vacuum every day.
他每天都用吸尘器这样做
No! hey! no!
天啊
Help! it's stuck! I can't get it off!
救命啊  塞住了  我不能把它取下来
Help! Help! it's stuck.
救命啊  塞住了
Gotcha.
逮住你了
Help!
救命
No!
不
She was using me. l...that was really bad.
她过去利用我  真糟糕
Father, why hast thou forsaken me?
神父  你为什么抛弃了我
Wanna suck me off in the sharper lmage?
想更淫荡地对我口淫吗
Rob, are you some kind of jive turkey?
罗伯  你是不是特会甜言蜜语啊
He's like an inch away from the real McCoy.
他都不像他本人了
Did you bring condoms?
带避孕套了吗
What?
什么
I wet the bed until I was 13 years old, okay?
我从13岁开始就想做爱了
You nancy boys couldn't get lucky at a Jonas Brothers concert
你们没有机会去乔纳斯兄弟的演唱会
With a fistful of backstage passes.
纵使有很多后台通行证
Faith in god and his promise of eternal life.
相信上帝和他对生命永恒的承诺
Now, put the condom on the banana.
现在  把避孕套套上香蕉
Who didn't see that coming? Look at the time. gotta go.
谁没有看到啊  看看时间  得走了
I think that is quite enough pictures of the cheerleaders.
我觉得关于拉拉队的照片太多了
How about we get some of the game?
照点比赛的
We're eating.
正吃着呢
You've been fucking americans or...
你们是该死的美国人吗
Watching, loving...
看着  爱着
Bear with me.
容忍我一下
If she's down, bring her flowers.
如果她沮丧  送她花
If she's thirsty, serve her fine champagne.
她渴了  给她来一杯香槟
Yeah, 'cause, I'm telling you, my wife is pretty effing hot.
我告诉你  我妻子太他妈性感了
I'm talking a tight, tight ass and squeaky clean.
我说的是十分紧十分干净的阴口
Is that cream-filled? You rock.
很多奶油吗  太好了
Oh. Don't mention that, okay?
拜托你别提了
And whenever it comes to making out,
做爱的时候
Put on side one of Led Zeppelin IV.
摆出齐柏林飞船四世(乐队)的架子